{
    "subject": "resource/Capture_of_USS_President",
    "predicate": "http://www.w3.org/2000/01/rdf-schema#label",
    "object": "Capture of USS President",
    "human_readable": "The label of Capture of USS President is 'Capture of USS President'.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9750187397003174,
            "question": "What is the label of the event 'Capture of USS President'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.938464343547821,
            "question": "Is the label of the event 'Capture of USS President' accurate?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8673708438873291,
            "question": "Where did the 'Capture of USS President' take place?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8601846098899841,
            "question": "Who were the parties involved in the 'Capture of USS President'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8534289002418518,
            "question": "Can you provide more details about the event 'Capture of USS President'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8338883519172668,
            "question": "What was the outcome of the 'Capture of USS President'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8316909670829773,
            "question": "When did the 'Capture of USS President' occur?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7720882892608643,
            "question": "What historical significance does the event 'Capture of USS President' hold?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7551782727241516,
            "question": "Are there any primary sources related to the 'Capture of USS President'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7423960566520691,
            "question": "How is the event 'Capture of USS President' remembered today?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The label of Capture of USS President is 'Capture of USS President'.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5373_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any primary sources related to the 'Capture of USS President'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5373_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What historical significance does the event 'Capture of USS President' hold?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5373_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=When did the 'Capture of USS President' occur?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5373_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5373_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5373_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5373_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5373_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5373_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5373_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5373_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5373_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5373_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5373_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON format for your query:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe query \"The label of Capture of USS President is 'Capture of USS President'\" matches the information provided in the documents, which states that one of the events associated with USS President (1800) was \"Capture of the USS President.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n    }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}